Bing Hu

Email: binghucnsty@gmail.com

Phone: (86)15712309691

Profile:

Full stack engineer/architect

I have 10+ years experience with web/backend/mobile development.

I worked as developer, architect and team leader etc and completed many projects successfully such as Travel booking services, delivery system, payment service, ERP and MES etc.

Past 6 years I worked as remote engineer and familiar with remote team work and flexible timezone.

I'm a passionate engineer, quick learner and don't afraid of new challenges.

I'll try to satisfy my clients with my best and it is just my value and happiness to make the client's business success.

Skills Summary:

Main focused area

- Travel Booking Service Development
- Delivery Service Development
- Payment Service Development
- ERP/MES/SCADA
- Other Web/Mobile Apps

Technical Stacks

- backend : golang/nodejs/asp.net/laravel/j2ee spring/Strapi
- front : reactjs/vuejs/angular/elixir/jsp/php
- app :react-native, iOS/android native

Others

- ibm cloud/AWS/Google cloud
- mysql/postgres/db2/mssql/oracle/mongodb
- docker/kubernates/Openshift
- firebase/kinvey
- Mqtt/Modbus/FIN/Opc-UA/HSMS etc

Qualifications:

Master's Degree of Computer Science

Languages:

Education:

- 2001 2006 Beijing Information Science & Technology University, Computer Science
- 2006 2008 Beijing Information Science & Technology University, Computer Science (Master's Degree)

Employment History:

ShengTianYang, China

Web/Mobile Developer

2010-2015

- Video CMS Development(AngularJS/Php)
- Cloud File Sharing Solution Development(Electron)
- Language Education System Development(Laravel)
- DLP Solution Development(Windows Kernel Driver/C++/J2ee)
- ETL Solution Development(Java/SWT)
- Police Support System(J2EE, android mobile)
- 1:1 online education system(iOS/Andoid)

Porcheson, China

Senior Engineer

2016-2017

- MES System development(golang, reactJS)
- ERP System development(ASP.NET, ReactJS)
- Scada System development(C++, Electron)

Neusis, United States(Remote)

Web/Mobile Developer

2016-2017

- Transport Delivery System(Angular, Nodejs)
- Skycoin Backend/Admin Panel Development(golang, angularJS)
- Tommy Now, Tommy Snipsnap, Roar for us, Milkcrate App development(React Native)
- Other eCommerce/Business homepage/Admin panels(Golang, Reactjs, Vuejs, Angularjs)

Room-Res, Australia(Remote)

S/W Architect/Engineer

2018-2020

- Hotel Booking Service Development(Golang, React.js, React-Native)
- Airline Booking Service Development(Golang, Vue.js)

Greenbay, UK(Remote)

S/W Team Leader/Architect

2020-2021

• Greenbay Payment System Development(Golang, ReactJS, NodeJS, Laravel, Solidity, blockchain)

Clarus R&D, United States (Remote)

Full stack engineer 2021.4~2021.10

- Tax Credit Payment System Development(Golang, React, Postgres)
- Tax Credit Payment System Development(Elixir, Phoenix/Liveview)